<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=12] -->
    <string name="app_name">Hamburg Travel Guide</string>

    <!-- Category name for food [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_food">Food</string>

    <!-- Category - food -->
    <string name="first_food_name">Bullerei</string>
    <string name="first_food_desc">Restaurant</string>
    <string name="first_food_full_desc">Bullerei seems to have it all: a beautiful building, great location
        (right around the corner from the Sternschanze S-Bahn station), fun atmosphere, and dining options for both casual and special occasions.
        Stop by for a deli lunch, sit outside with a sandwich or burger, or get a table in the restaurant and enjoy the creative dinner menu.
        \nSteaks/meat dishes are the restaurant\'s specialties, they also do have vegetarian dishes and are happy to accommodate special requests or
        to recommend options for non-meat eaters.</string>
    <string name="first_food_address">Sternschanze, 20357 Hamburg, Germany</string>
    <string name="first_food_phone">+49 40 33442110</string>

    <string name="second_food_name">Elbgold</string>
    <string name="second_food_desc">Coffeehouse</string>
    <string name="second_food_full_desc">Elbgold has the reputation for serving \'the best coffee in the city\' — or at least in this part of the city.
        With its own coffee roastery, the cafe definitely feels like a place that\'s really passionate about the art of coffee. Bagel sandwiches, pastries,
        and cakes complete the experience, making it a great place for brunch, lunch, or an afternoon break.
        \nTry the Franzbrötchen (sweet pastry, usually cinnamon-flavored), which is a typical Hamburg breakfast/brunch item, and goes great with coffee!</string>
    <string name="second_food_address">Lagerstraße 32, 20357 Hamburg, Germany</string>
    <string name="second_food_phone">+49 40 23517520</string>

    <string name="third_food_name">Koppel</string>
    <string name="third_food_desc">Cafe</string>
    <string name="third_food_full_desc">Located in the \'Koppel66 Art and Craft House\' in the fashionable St. Georg area, Cafe Koppel is especially
        great for lunch/brunch in the summer, as it has a great outdoor garden area. With a daily menu, homemade cakes, and of course coffee,
        this is also one of the best vegetarian options in this part of Hamburg.
        \nSometimes they run out of their daily specialties. Go earlier in the day for more choice.</string>
    <string name="third_food_address">Lange Reihe 75, 20099 Hamburg, Germany</string>
    <string name="third_food_phone">+49 40 249235</string>

    <string name="fourth_food_name">Thämers</string>
    <string name="fourth_food_desc">Bar</string>
    <string name="fourth_food_full_desc">Thämers is another great spot in the Großneumarkt area, which is an easy walking distance from the famous St. Michael\'s church.
        What many people think of as \'typical German food\' is often typical of southern Germany. Hamburg/northern Germany has its own local food traditions,
        and at Thämers you can try out some northern specialties in a cozy, \'old-school\' local pub atmosphere.
        \nNot all servers speak English, but they are all friendly and helpful, and you can also request an English menu.
        For those who don\'t eat meat or fish, the selection is limited.</string>
    <string name="fourth_food_address">Grossneumarkt 10, 20459 Hamburg, Germany</string>
    <string name="fourth_food_phone">+49 40 345077</string>


    <!-- Category name for sights [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_sights">Sights</string>

    <!-- Category - sights -->
    <string name="first_sight_name">Town Hall</string>
    <string name="first_sight_desc">Hamburg\'s Old Town</string>
    <string name="first_sight_full_desc">If this is your first time in Hamburg, then a good starting point would be the area around the Jungfernstieg.
        You will find yourself by the Binnenalster – an artificial lake, which is fed by the river Alster.
        There are some magnificent buildingsalong the shores of the Binnenalster. Just a few minutes walk from the Jungfernstieg is one of the most
        beautiful buildings in Hamburg: the town hall. This Neo-Renaissance building is not only surprisingly large, but also incredibly beautiful.
        The courtyard of the town hall is also very worth seeing if you’re in the area.</string>
    <string name="first_sight_address">Rathausmarkt 1, 20095 Hamburg, Germany</string>

    <string name="second_sight_name"> St. Michael\'s church</string>
    <string name="second_sight_desc">Main Church of St. Michaelis</string>
    <string name="second_sight_full_desc">The most famous church in Hamburg is nicknamed the Michel. You can get here from the town hall in about
        15 minutes by foot. You can either walk up the tower (453 steps) or choose to go up with the lift – the price is actually the same for both options.
        The 360-degree view from high above Hamburg is just stunning and although you are behind safety bars, you can easily photograph through them.
        For a super unique experience, you could also visit at night.They call this Nachtmichel (or Night Michel in English) and you can visit in the
        evenings, past regular opening hours, on many days of the year. However, the prices are a little higher.</string>
    <string name="second_sight_address">St. Michael\'s Church, Englische Planke, Hamburg, Germany</string>

    <string name="third_sight_name">Planten un Blomen</string>
    <string name="third_sight_desc">Park</string>
    <string name="third_sight_full_desc">Planten un Blomen, which roughly translates to “Plants and Flowers”, is a large urban park in the middle of Hamburg.
        It\'s an excellent escape on a nice day so pack a picnic and some adult beverages and enjoy nature. It\'s also famous for having Europe largest Japanese
        garden and an impressive tropical greenhouse complex. There are also a number of playgrounds and other attractions for the kiddos.
        Stadtpark, often called the “Green Heart” of Hamburg, is a huge park in the northern part of the city that locals flock to during the nice weather.
        The park features dozens of statues, a lake, playgrounds, a large lawn, and wooded areas.</string>
    <string name="third_sight_address">Planten un Blomen, Marseiller Straße, Hamburg, Germany</string>

    <string name="fourth_sight_name">Miniatur Wunderland</string>
    <string name="fourth_sight_desc">Museum</string>
    <string name="fourth_sight_full_desc">The Miniatur Wunderland is not only the largest model railway in the world, but it’s also the most popular tourist
        attraction in Germany. Before going we thought it would be a bit kitschy (and it is) but it’s actually a lot of fun. They’ve built multiple massive
        scenes that are modeled around different parts of the world (and they’re adding more every year). But the real joy is taking the time to admire all
        the details and easter eggs of each scene. And yes, some of the little figurines are a bit naughty.</string>
    <string name="fourth_sight_address">Miniatur Wunderland, Kehrwieder, Hamburg, Germany</string>


    <!-- Category name for tours [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_tours">Tours</string>

    <string name="first_tour_name">Harbour Cruise</string>
    <string name="first_tour_desc">Sightseeing activity</string>
    <string name="first_tour_full_desc">A typical sightseeing activity for Hamburg usually includes a harbour cruise. Exploring Hamburg from the water is
        such a unique and special experience – we can only highly recommend you experience it for yourselves. There are countless providers offering harbour
        cruises with a variety of ships and routes. However, we would recommend you take one of the smaller boats (called barges), because only these small
        boats will pass through the narrower canals (in the Hamburg Fleete) of the Speicherstadt. Most ships depart from the Landungsbrücken and when you get
        there, be prepared to be overwhelmed by the amount of harbour cruise offers.</string>
    <string name="first_tour_address">Landungsbrücken, Kuhberg, Hamburg, Germany</string>

    <string name="second_tour_name">Alsterrundfahrt Tour</string>
    <string name="second_tour_desc">Tour along the River</string>
    <string name="second_tour_full_desc">The second most popular boat tour in Hamburg would be the Alsterrundfahrt Tour – along the Alster River.The classic
        Alsterrundfahrt starts at the Jungfernstieg and takes you across the Binnenalster and the Außenalster for about 1 hour. As you cruise along the shore,
        you’ll learn some background information about Hamburg and specific individual buildings along the tour.</string>
    <string name="second_tour_address">Alster, Hamburg, Germany</string>

    <string name="third_tour_name">Free Walking Tours</string>
    <string name="third_tour_desc">Sightseeing activity</string>
    <string name="third_tour_full_desc">One of the best ways to get a nice overview of Hamburg is through a free walking tour. Their Historic City Center tour
        gave a nice overview of Hamburg’s history and you see a lot of the classic sights like St Michael’s Church, the Rathaus, Nikolaifleet (the old canal).
        Also St. Pauli &amp; Reeperbahn tour — which covers some of the seedier parts of the city’s past. Another interesting option is to request to get
        shown around town by local volunteer greeters via Hamburg Greeter. This is a volunteer organization so you need to request a greeter at least two
        weeks in advance.</string>
    <string name="third_tour_address">Malzweg 13, Hamburg, Germany</string>

    <string name="fourth_tour_name">Donkey Republic</string>
    <string name="fourth_tour_desc">Explore on bike</string>
    <string name="fourth_tour_full_desc">While Hamburg might not be as bike-friendly as its Scandinavian neighbors, bikes are still a popular form of
        transportation and there is a decent number of dedicated bike lanes. Like most cities in Europe, Hamburg has its own bike sharing program (StadtRAD)
        where you can check out bikes from automated stations throughout the city. You’ll need to first create an account on StradtRAD — the first 30-minutes
        is free and then rentals cost 8 cents per minute with a maximum fee of €12 per day. In addition to private businesses that rent bikes, you’ll also see
        bright orange bikes scattered throughout the city from a company called Donkey Republic — you use a smartphone app to find and unlock the bikes.
        Prices start at 1.25 for 30 minutes and you just park the bike wherever you like when finished.</string>
    <string name="fourth_tour_address">Neuer Pferdemarkt 12, 20359 Hamburg, Germany</string>

    <!-- Category name for views [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_views">Views</string>

    <string name="first_view_name">Elbphilharmonie</string>
    <string name="first_view_desc">37 meters high</string>
    <string name="first_view_full_desc">The recently opened Elbphilharmonie Concert Hall is the largest and acoustically most advanced concert halls in the
        world. This €870 million jewel of the Hamburg skyline is made to look like the ocean waves. Concert tickets are tough to score (and they’re not cheap)
        but you can visit the 360-degree view observation decks for €2 (you canbook tickets online to skip the line).</string>
    <string name="first_view_address">Elbphilharmonie, Platz der Deutschen Einheit, Hamburg, Germany</string>

    <string name="second_view_name">Planetarium</string>
    <string name="second_view_desc">70 meters high</string>
    <string name="second_view_full_desc">This former water tower is now home to the planetarium and offers a viewing platform at the roof during the opening
        hours which is free of charge. From here you can observe the wide Stadtpark, the City Nord and the nearby airport.</string>
    <string name="second_view_address">22303 Hamburg, Germany</string>

    <string name="third_view_name">Dockland</string>
    <string name="third_view_desc">40 meters over the river Elbe</string>
    <string name="third_view_full_desc">Down by the river you can find this modern structure – a building which looks like a ship. Use the many stairs
        to get to the observation deck on top of the building and enjoy one of the best views across the harbour!</string>
    <string name="third_view_address">Van-der-Smissen-Straße 9, 22767 Hamburg, Germany</string>

    <string name="fourth_view_name">Michel</string>
    <string name="fourth_view_desc">132 meters high</string>
    <string name="fourth_view_full_desc">The inside of the church is well worth seeing, but the Michel is best known for its church tower: high up at the observation
        deck of the 132-meter-high tower, you can enjoy a magnificent panoramic view of the city. Though this is the only one which isn\'t free it\'s worth spending the 5€ as the view from the St. Michael\'s church
        is possibly the best view in town as you are able to enjoy a 360 degree view to all parts of the city. In combination with the interior of the church
        it is definitely one of the best things to do in Hamburg. Every now and then there is an event called “Nachtmichel” where you are able to access the
        platform at night, a ticket is 10,50€.</string>
    <string name="fourth_view_address">St. Michael\'s Church, Englische Planke, Hamburg, Germany</string>

</resources>